Simon Fraser University Library fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Collections Division records, 1965 - 1992; F-50-3; 1.13 m of textual records
  - Special projects and foundations, 1966 - 1980; F-50-3-3; 44 cm of textual records
    - Institutional Correspondence - Q (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1973 - 1976; F-50-3-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - R (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1974; F-50-3-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - S (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1972 - 1973; F-50-3-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - T (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1972 - 1973; F-50-3-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - U (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1973; F-50-3-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - V (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1973 - 1974; F-50-3-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - W (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1971 - 1976; F-50-3-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - X, Y, Z (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1971 - 1975; F-50-3-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Catalogue, 1971; F-50-3-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Canada Council Library grants - applications, 1966 - 1968; F-50-3-3-0-30 (Archival box - small 50-26)
    - Hassan African collection - correspondence, 1966 - 1967; F-50-3-3-0-31 (Archival box - small 50-26)
    - Collection evaluations - reports, 1970 - 1971; F-50-3-3-0-32 (Archival box - small 50-26)
    - Departmental collections/libraries - correspondence, 1969 - 1972; F-50-3-3-0-33 (Archival box - small 50-26)
    - Guides to literature, 1970 - 1973; F-50-3-3-0-34 (Archival box - small 50-26)
    - Vancouver Foundation, 1966 - 1980; F-50-3-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 50-81)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7003/16.
    - The Boag Foundation, 1976 - 1979; F-50-3-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 50-81)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7003/12.
    - Dr. Charles Ed. Borden, 1976 - 1979; F-50-3-3-0-37 (Archival box - standard 50-81)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7003/11.
    - Talon Books, 1975 - 1977; F-50-3-3-0-38 (Archival box - standard 50-82)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7003/8.
    - Donner Foundation, vol. 1, 1968 - 1974; F-50-3-3-0-39 (Archival box - standard 50-82)
    - Donner Foundation, vol. 2, 1968 - 1974; F-50-3-3-0-40 (Archival box - standard 50-82)
    - RCMP collection, 1970 - 1975; F-50-3-3-0-41 (Archival box - standard 50-82)
      Creator's original file classification code: 8000/19.
- Processing Division records, 1967 - 1977; F-50-4; 26 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to the activities of the Processing Division of the University Library and includes correspondence with the university community, other university libraries, and professional associations; staff reference letters; faculty book processing requests; college book processing procedures; and budget planning and operating expenses for the division.
  Records include correspondence and working papers, minutes, statistics and financial statements.
  The individual records in this series are filed chronologically as this was the original filing system of the creator.
  - Memoranda, 1967 - 1968; F-50-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-27)
  - Memoranda, 1969 - 1970; F-50-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-27)
  - Memoranda, 1971 - 1977; F-50-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-27)
  - Memoranda, Acquisition, 1968 - 1970; F-50-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-27)
  - Memoranda, Allocation, 1968 - 1969; F-50-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-27)
  - Memoranda, Binding, 1968 - 1969; F-50-4-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-27)
  - Memoranda, Personnel, 1971 - 1973; F-50-4-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-27)
  - Memoranda, Serials, 1967 - 1969; F-50-4-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-27)
  - Memoranda, Systems, 1967 - 1969; F-50-4-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-27)
  - Memoranda, Sys/Planning and Budget, 1969 - 1974; F-50-4-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-27)
  - Correspondence, 1967; F-50-4-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-28)
  - Correspondence, 1968; F-50-4-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-28)
  - Correspondence, 1969; F-50-4-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-28)
  - Correspondence, 1970; F-50-4-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-28)
  - Correspondence, 1970; F-50-4-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-28)
  - Correspondence, 1971; F-50-4-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-28)
  - Correspondence, 1972; F-50-4-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-28)
  - Correspondence, 1973; F-50-4-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-28)
  - Correspondence, 1973; F-50-4-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 50-28)
  - Correspondence, 1974; F-50-4-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 50-28)
  - Correspondence, 1974; F-50-4-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 50-28)
  - Correspondence, 1975; F-50-4-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 50-28)
  - Correspondence, 1975; F-50-4-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 50-28)
- Acquisitions Division records, 1964 - 1988; F-50-5; 48 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to the establishment of the Library collection and includes the Library's original book accession lists; Acquisitions Division correspondence with the university community and book processing and publishing companies; annual reports for the division; and work of the Serials Project Team.
  Records include correspondence, reports, statistics, and invoices.
  Acquisitions Division correspondence from the years 1966, 1967, 1968 and 1973 is missing but has been included in the file list.
  - Library establishment accessions, 1964 - 1969; F-50-5-1; 12 cm of textual records 20 rolls of microfilm
    Accession lists are arranged alphabetically.
    - Original Accession List - A, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - B, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - C, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - D, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - E, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - F, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - G, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - H, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - I, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - J, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - K, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - L, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - M, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - N, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - O, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - P, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - Q, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - R, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - S, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - T, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - U-V, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - W, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - X, Y, Z, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
    - Original Accession List - Sets, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 50-29)
  - Correspondence and memoranda, 1964 - 1988; F-50-5-2; 36 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence - Alanar Book Processing, 1964 - 1965; F-50-5-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-31)
    - Correspondence - Gifts, 1964 - 1970; F-50-5-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-31)
    - Correspondence, 1964; F-50-5-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-31)
    - Correspondence, 1965; F-50-5-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-31)
    - Correspondence - missing, 1966; F-50-5-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-31)
    - Correspondence - missing, 1967; F-50-5-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-31)
    - Correspondence - missing, 1968; F-50-5-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-31)
    - Correspondence, 1969; F-50-5-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-31)
    - Correspondence, 1970; F-50-5-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-31)
    - Correspondence, 1971; F-50-5-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-31)
    - Correspondence, 1972; F-50-5-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-31)
    - Correspondence - missing, 1973; F-50-5-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-31)
    - Correspondence, 1974; F-50-5-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-31)
    - Correspondence, 1975; F-50-5-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-31)
    - Correspondence, 1976; F-50-5-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-31)
    - Reports, 1969 - 1971; F-50-5-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-32)
    - Memoranda, 1969 - 1975; F-50-5-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-32)
    - Annual Reports, 1970 - 1974; F-50-5-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-32)
    - Statistics, 1968 - 1970; F-50-5-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 50-32)
    - ABEL approvals, 1969 - 1972; F-50-5-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 50-32)
    - COUTTS U.S. approvals, 1973 - 1975; F-50-5-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 50-32)
    - COUTTS Canadian approvals, 1973 - 1975; F-50-5-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 50-32)
    - BLACKWELL approvals, 1973 - 1975; F-50-5-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 50-32)
    - Serials memoranda, 1967 - 1980; F-50-5-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 50-32)
    - Serials memoranda, 1981 - 1988; F-50-5-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 50-32)
    - Acquisitions - Serials Project Team, 1974 - 1976; F-50-5-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 50-82)
    - Serials section, 1974 - 1977; F-50-5-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 50-82)
    - Accessions, 1969 - 1973; F-50-5-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 50-82)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/25.
    - Canada Council, 1964 - 1967; F-50-5-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 50-83)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7003/5.
    - Canada Council, 1967; F-50-5-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 50-83)
    - Acquisitions correspondence, 1969 - 1987; F-50-5-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 50-83)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/23.
- Cataloguing Division records, 1965 - 1988; F-50-6; 67 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the activities of the Cataloguing Division at the University Library and includes correspondence with the university community; division organizational charts; monthly division activity reports, cataloguing statistics, and annual reports; division budget planning; and procedures for carrying out shared cataloguing and processing for regional colleges in British Columbia.
  Records include correspondence, reports, statistics, budgets and financial working papers.
  - General correspondence, 1965 - 1988; F-50-6-1; 14 cm of textual records
    - Organization Charts, 1965 - 1975; F-50-6-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-33)
    - Correspondence, 1968; F-50-6-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-33)
    - Correspondence, 1969; F-50-6-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-33)
    - Correspondence, 1970; F-50-6-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-33)
    - Correspondence, 1971; F-50-6-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-33)
    - Correspondence, 1972; F-50-6-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-33)
    - Correspondence, 1973; F-50-6-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-33)
    - Correspondence, 1974; F-50-6-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-33)
    - Correspondence, 1975; F-50-6-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-33)
    - Correspondence, 1976; F-50-6-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-33)
    - Correspondence, 1982 - 1983; F-50-6-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-33)
    - Correspondence, 1984 - 1988; F-50-6-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-33)
    - Correspondence, 1968 - 1985; F-50-6-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-83)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/24.
  - Reports, 1967 - 1977; F-50-6-2; 13 cm of textual records
    Reports are arranged chronologically.
    - Monthly Reports, 1967 - 1968; F-50-6-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-34)
    - Monthly Reports, 1970 - 1971; F-50-6-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-34)
    - Monthly Reports, 1971 - 1972; F-50-6-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-34)
    - Monthly Reports, 1972 - 1973; F-50-6-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-34)
    - Monthly Reports, 1973 - 1974; F-50-6-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-34)
    - Monthly Reports, 1974 - 1975; F-50-6-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-34)
    - Monthly Reports, 1975 - 1976; F-50-6-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-34)
    - Monthly Reports, 1976 - 1977; F-50-6-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-34)
    - Annual Reports, 1968 - 1977; F-50-6-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-34)
  - Statistics, 1966 - 1977; F-50-6-3; 7 cm of textual records
    Statistics sheets are arranged chronologically.
    - Statistics, 1966 - 1967; F-50-6-3-0-1 (Archival box - small 50-35)
    - Statistics, 1967 - 1968; F-50-6-3-0-2 (Archival box - small 50-35)
    - Statistics, 1968 - 1969; F-50-6-3-0-3 (Archival box - small 50-35)
    - Statistics, 1969 - 1970; F-50-6-3-0-4 (Archival box - small 50-35)
    - Statistics, 1970 - 1971; F-50-6-3-0-5 (Archival box - small 50-35)
    - Statistics, 1971 - 1972; F-50-6-3-0-6 (Archival box - small 50-35)
    - Statistics, 1972 - 1973; F-50-6-3-0-7 (Archival box - small 50-35)
    - Statistics, 1973 - 1974; F-50-6-3-0-8 (Archival box - small 50-35)
    - Statistics, 1974 - 1975; F-50-6-3-0-9 (Archival box - small 50-35)
    - Statistics, 1975 - 1976; F-50-6-3-0-10 (Archival box - small 50-35)
    - Statistics, 1976 - 1977; F-50-6-3-0-11 (Archival box - small 50-35)
  - Budget, 1965 - 1976; F-50-6-4; 12 cm of textual records
    Records are arranged chronologically.
    - Budget, 1965 - 1966; F-50-6-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-36)
    - Budget, 1966 - 1967; F-50-6-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-36)
    - Budget, 1967 - 1968; F-50-6-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-36)
    - Budget, 1968 - 1969; F-50-6-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-36)
    - Budget, 1969 - 1970; F-50-6-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-36)
    - Budget, 1970 - 1971; F-50-6-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-36)
    - Budget, 1971 - 1972; F-50-6-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-36)
    - Budget, 1972 - 1973; F-50-6-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-36)
    - Budget, 1973 - 1974; F-50-6-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-36)
    - Budget, 1974 - 1975; F-50-6-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-36)
    - Budget, 1975 - 1976; F-50-6-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-36)
  - Shared cataloguing, 1969 - 1973; F-50-6-5; 6 cm of textual records
    - Tick Tracing Conversion Project, 1971 - 1972; F-50-6-5-0-1 (Archival box - small 50-37)
    - Shared Cataloging, 1969 - 1970; F-50-6-5-0-2 (Archival box - small 50-37)
    - Shared Cataloging, 1971; F-50-6-5-0-3 (Archival box - small 50-37)
    - Shared Cataloging, 1972; F-50-6-5-0-4 (Archival box - small 50-37)
    - Shared Cataloging, 1973; F-50-6-5-0-5 (Archival box - small 50-37)
    - Shared Cataloging, 1970 - 1972; F-50-6-5-0-6 (Archival box - small 50-37)
    - Serials Cataloging, 1971; F-50-6-5-0-7 (Archival box - small 50-37)
  - College processing, 1970 - 1977; F-50-6-6; 16 cm of textual records
    - College Processing, 1970 - 1971; F-50-6-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-38)
    - College Processing, 1971 - 1972; F-50-6-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-38)
    - College Processing, 1972 - 1973; F-50-6-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-38)
    - College Processing, 1973 - 1974; F-50-6-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-38)
    - College Processing, 1974 - 1975; F-50-6-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-38)
    - College Processing, 1975 - 1976; F-50-6-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-38)
    - College Processing, 1976 - 1977; F-50-6-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-38)
    - College Contracts, 1971 - 1975; F-50-6-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-38)
    - College Processing Statistics, 1971 - 1973; F-50-6-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-38)
    - College Summaries, 1974 - 1975; F-50-6-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-38)
    - College Processing Procedures, 1974; F-50-6-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-38)
    - College Processing Monthly Reports, 1974 - 1975; F-50-6-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-38)
    - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1970 - 1974; F-50-6-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-83)
    - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1970 - 1974; F-50-6-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-83)
- Loans Division records, 1964 - 1998; F-50-7; 1.74 m of textual records
  Series consists of records related to the activities of the Loans Division of the University Library and includes correspondence with the university community; policy development on loan procedures including on-line and external; annual reports, monthly Division activity reports, and turnstile statistics; Division meeting minutes; Division budget planning and financial working documents; reports including information on staff activities, workload, projects, the 24 hour Library opening experiment, and on the SHARE project with Okanagan College in Kelowna; interlibrary loans procedures between SFU and the University of British Columbia, progress reports and statistics; and participation in the B.C. Post Secondary Interlibrary Loan Network.
  Records include correspondence, minutes, reports, questionnaires, statistics, policies, and financial working papers.
  University of British Columbia (UBC)
  - Correspondence and memoranda, 1965 - 1988; F-50-7-1; 83 cm of textual records
    - File index and chronological correspondence, 1980; F-50-7-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-39)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1980; F-50-7-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-39)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1981; F-50-7-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-39)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1981; F-50-7-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-39)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1982; F-50-7-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-39)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1982; F-50-7-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-39)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1983; F-50-7-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-39)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1983; F-50-7-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-39)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1984; F-50-7-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-39)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1984; F-50-7-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-39)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1985; F-50-7-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-40)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1985; F-50-7-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-40)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1986; F-50-7-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-40)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1986; F-50-7-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-40)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1987; F-50-7-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-40)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1987; F-50-7-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-40)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1988; F-50-7-1-0-17 (Archival box - small 50-41)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1988; F-50-7-1-0-18 (Archival box - small 50-41)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1988; F-50-7-1-0-19 (Archival box - small 50-41)
    - Memoranda, 1965 - 1969; F-50-7-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 50-42)
    - Memoranda, 1980; F-50-7-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 50-42)
    - Memoranda, 1980; F-50-7-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 50-42)
    - Memoranda, 1981; F-50-7-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 50-42)
    - Memoranda, 1981; F-50-7-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 50-42)
    - Memoranda, 1982; F-50-7-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 50-42)
    - Memoranda, 1982; F-50-7-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 50-42)
    - Memoranda, 1983; F-50-7-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 50-42)
    - Memoranda, 1983; F-50-7-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 50-42)
    - Memoranda, 1984; F-50-7-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 50-42)
    - Memoranda, 1984; F-50-7-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 50-43)
    - Memoranda, 1984; F-50-7-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 50-43)
    - Memoranda, 1985; F-50-7-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 50-43)
    - Memoranda, 1985; F-50-7-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 50-43)
    - Memoranda, 1986; F-50-7-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 50-43)
    - Memoranda, 1986; F-50-7-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 50-43)
    - Memoranda, 1986; F-50-7-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 50-43)
    - Memoranda, 1986; F-50-7-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 50-43)
    - Memoranda, 1988; F-50-7-1-0-38 (Archival box - small 50-44)
    - Memoranda, 1988; F-50-7-1-0-39 (Archival box - small 50-44)
    - Memoranda, 1988; F-50-7-1-0-40 (Archival box - small 50-44)
    - Memoranda, 1988; F-50-7-1-0-41 (Archival box - small 50-44)
    - Fine Arts loan policy, vol. 1, 1980 - 1984; F-50-7-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 50-84)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/38.
    - Fine Arts loan policy, vol. 2, 1980 - 1984; F-50-7-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 50-84)
    - Loans - on-line, 1968 - 1984; F-50-7-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 50-84)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/34/2.
    - Loans Division Group leaders meetings, 1981 - 1988; F-50-7-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 50-84)
      Creator's original file classification code: 400/2.
    - Evening Loans - reorganization, 1982; F-50-7-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 50-84)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/34/4.
    - Loans - organization and operations correspondence, vol. 1, 1966 - 1980; F-50-7-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 50-84)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/34.
    - Loans - organization and operations correspondence, vol. 2, 1966 - 1980; F-50-7-1-0-48 (Archival box - standard 50-85)
    - Loans - organization and operations correspondence, vol. 3, 1966 - 1980; F-50-7-1-0-49 (Archival box - standard 50-85)
    - Loans - organization and operations correspondence, vol. 4, 1966 - 1980; F-50-7-1-0-50 (Archival box - standard 50-85)
  - Reports and statistics, 1965 - 1998; F-50-7-2; 31 cm of textual records
    - Group Leaders Meetings, 1974 - 1980; F-50-7-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-45)
    - Manual of procedures for Student Assistants, 1968; F-50-7-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-45)
    - Lost Books Policy, 1968 - 1973; F-50-7-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-45)
    - SHARE Project, 1978 - 1980; F-50-7-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-45)
    - Temporary Employees, 1977 - 1980; F-50-7-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-45)
    - Workload assessment, 1974; F-50-7-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-45)
    - 24 Hour Opening Experiment, 1982; F-50-7-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-45)
    - 24 Hour: Questionnaire, 1982; F-50-7-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-45)
    - External Loans, 1975 - 1979; F-50-7-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-45)
    - External Statistics, 1975 - [198-]; F-50-7-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-45)
    - Annual Reports, 1966 - 1977; F-50-7-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-46)
    - Monthly Reports, 1973; F-50-7-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-46)
    - Monthly Reports, 1974; F-50-7-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-46)